Day 33 of DSA series. In this video we understand the lead call problem number 42. This question
is asked in midflix, flip card and google. Here, wrapping rain water means here. These
are the building blocks after raining. The water will be stored between these building
apps. So, by using this formula, we find the how much of total water is stored in between
these building apps. Here approach is step 1. We find the lift maximum. Here lift maximum
is 4. So, we take the 4 and step 2. Right maximum is 5. So, we take the all lift 4 and
the maximum right is 5. And here last index 5 is, we take the index 5 is 5. So, it is
the lift maximum. Lift maximum is 5 and right maximum is also 5. And step 3, we apply the
formula here. Lift maximum and right maximum. Here we take the minimum. Minimum is 4. So, 4
minus the height of index 0 is 4. 4 minus 4 is 0. So, here 0. Again index 1 is the height
of index 2 is 2. So, here the minimum element is 4. 4 minus 2. Here the 2 is stored. And
your index 2 is here. Index height of index 2 is 0. Here 4 minus 0. 4. Again here, height
of index 3 is 3. So, here 4 minus 3. 1. So, here 1 is stored. I can take 4. Here, height
of index 4 is 2. So, here 4 minus 2 is 2. Here 2 is stored. Maximum left is 5. And
maximum right is also 5. And 5 minus 5 is 0. So, here 0 is stored. And step 4, we add
the all elements. Here 2 plus 4 plus 1 plus 2 here. Total is 9. So, here the output is
9. Comment code and I will send it directly in your DMs.